Digital Media Department Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; nam_ua395-6; 93.44 GB 67737 Digital Files
  - Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; nam_ua395-6.1; 75.21 GB 56337 Digital Files
    - Development Events: 10/19/05 full day / NYC locations Foundation Board Mtg/ NYC Alumni Event digital, 2005 September 23; nam_ua395-6.1_189; 464.9 MB 232 Digital Files
    - President: 10/7/05 @ 3 PM Alumni House Moot Court Demonstration digital, 2005 October 17; nam_ua395-6.1_190; 109.3 MB 44 Digital Files
    - President: 10/11/05 @ 7:30 PM Page Hall Spike Lee digital, 2005 October 25; nam_ua395-6.1_191; 101.8 MB 65 Digital Files
    - President: 10/24/05 @ 2 PM PAC Recital Hall Brian Lamb interview digital, 2005 November 7; nam_ua395-6.1_192; 80.7 MB 50 Digital Files
    - Academic Events: 11/8/05 @ 4 PM PAC recital hall Distinguished Professor: Ron Bosco digital, 2005 November 15; nam_ua395-6.1_193; 143.2 MB 35 Digital Files
    - President: 11/1/05 @ 8:30 AM CC Ballroom Joanne Woodard: Winning in the Workplace digital, 2005 November 15; nam_ua395-6.1_194; 134.1 MB 81 Digital Files
    - President: 11/2/05 @ 8:45 AM Standish Room Executive Committee Mtg and President for a day digital, 2005 November 16; nam_ua395-6.1_195; 18.1 MB 13 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 11/10/05 @ 10 AM Standish Room Press Conf: Hurricane Katrina Relief Fund digital, 2005 November 16; nam_ua395-6.1_196; 91.9 MB 47 Digital Files
    - President: 11/2/05 @ 12:30 PM Milne 200 SSW Faculty Meeting digital, 2005 November 16; nam_ua395-6.1_197; 42.3 MB 25 Digital Files
    - President: 11/9/05 @ 8 - 9 AM CC Patroon Room Lounge Faculty Promotion Coffee digital, 2005 November 16; nam_ua395-6.1_198; 101.8 MB 23 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 11/9/05 @ 11:30 AM CC Ballroom FBI recruitment event difital, 2005 November 23; nam_ua395-6.1_199; 133.2 MB 30 Digital Files
    - President: 11/16/05 @ 11:30 AM Science Library / Barnes and Noble Room Just for Kids Announcement digital, 2005 November 30; nam_ua395-6.1_200; 373.2 MB 77 Digital Files
    - President: 12/12/05 @ 1 PM Science Library Check Presentation / Michael Orsino & Mitchell Miller digital, 2005 December 15; nam_ua395-6.1_201; 62.9 MB 13 Digital Files
    - President: 12/13/05 @ 7:45 AM Life Science Bldg / Auditorium Business Higher Education Roundtable (BHER) Fall Symposia / Dr. Bruce Katz digital, 2005 December 15; nam_ua395-6.1_202; 277.9 MB 52 Digital Files
    - President: 12/1/05 @ 1:30 PM Standish Room Press Conference / Announcement ot Honors College, 2005 December 15; nam_ua395-6.1_203; 152.0 MB 36 Digital Files
    - Advancement Events: 12/15/05 @ 6 PM - 8 PM Pres Res President's Holiday Toast, 2005 December 16; nam_ua395-6.1_204; 654.8 MB 116 Digital Files
    - President: 12/13/05 @ 2 PM George Bldg. East Campus NYS Power Authority and Senator Bruno, 2005 December 26; nam_ua395-6.1_205; 159.4 MB 28 Digital Files
    - President: 12/13/05 @ 3 PM CC Ballroom Destination Diploma Program, 2005 December 26; nam_ua395-6.1_206; 131.6 MB 22 Digital Files
    - President: 12/20/05 @ 1 PM NYS Museum NYS Archives Partnership Trust Tour, 2005 December 29; nam_ua395-6.1_207; 438.3 MB 81 Digital Files
    - Move in 2006, 1980 January 1; nam_ua395-6.1_208; 134.2 MB 112 Digital Files
    - Ctr for Small Business Development: 1/10/06 @ 3 pm Northern Industrial Services 1843 Central Ave. Colonie Industrial portrait, 2006 January 20; nam_ua395-6.1_209; 74.0 MB 24 Digital Files
    - President: 1/17/06 @ 6 PM - 7:30 PM Crowne Plaza Hotel Albany Business Council of NYS, 2006 January 26; nam_ua395-6.1_210; 7.1 MB 3 Digital Files
    - President: 1/17/06 @ 6 PM - 7:30 PM Crowne Plaza Hotel Albany Business Council of NYS, 2006 January 26; nam_ua395-6.1_211; 7.1 MB 3 Digital Files
    - Minority Health Disparities: 2/27/06 @ 11 AM A&S Building / outside? Group photo: Program Executive Committee, 2006 February 7; nam_ua395-6.1_212; 33.1 MB 14 Digital Files
    - President: 2/9/06 @ 12 Noon CC Ballroom Martin Luther King Jr. Luncheon, 2006 February 10; nam_ua395-6.1_213; 188.1 MB 90 Digital Files
    - President: 2/2/06 @ 3 PM Science Library Moscow Delegation w/ John Rohrbaugh, 2006 February 10; nam_ua395-6.1_214; 9.5 MB 5 Digital Files
    - President: 2/2/06 @ 10 AM Science Library DWI Exhibit w/ James Anderson, 2006 February 15; nam_ua395-6.1_215; 123.6 MB 58 Digital Files
    - President: 2/2/06 @ 12 Noon President's Office Joe Bowman and Johanna Duncan-Portier, 2006 February 16; nam_ua395-6.1_216; 18.5 MB 9 Digital Files
    - Alumni Affairs: 6/2/06 @ 6 PM Desmond Hotel Latham Gala Awards / Alumni Weekend, 2006 February 20; nam_ua395-6.1_217; 206.9 MB 99 Digital Files
    - Alumni Affairs: 6/3/06 @ Various times and locations class portraits, 2006 February 20; nam_ua395-6.1_218; 461.6 MB 197 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 2/17/06 @ 9:15 AM Cancer Research Center various lab shots, 2006 March 3; nam_ua395-6.1_219; 358.8 MB 179 Digital Files
    - Alumni Affairs: 3/2/06 @ 9 AM Alumni House UAlbany apparel, 2006 March 14; nam_ua395-6.1_220; 126.8 MB 21 Digital Files
    - President: 3/6/06 @ 9 AM location TBA Board of Visitors, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_221; 112.1 MB 56 Digital Files
    - President: 3/6/06 @ Noon location TBA Board of Visitors Luncheon, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_222; 40.4 MB 15 Digital Files
    - President: 3/7/06 @ 10:45 AM Capital Bldg. Albany SUNY Day, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_223; 82.9 MB 40 Digital Files
    - President: 3/10/06 Time and location TBA New Jobs NY w/ Hilary Clinton, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_224; 224.8 MB 105 Digital Files
    - President: 3/12/06 @ time TBA CC President's Leadership Awards Ceremony, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_225; 394.1 MB 101 Digital Files
    - President: 3/13/06 @ Noon - 1:30 PM CC (Ballroom or Assembly Hall) Minority Scholars Lunch for Albany High, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_226; 61.9 MB 30 Digital Files
    - President: 3/20/06 @ 2:30 PM Life Science Bldg Presentations for Board of Visitors, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_227; 48.9 MB 26 Digital Files
    - President: 3/20/06 @ 5:45 PM Milne 200 Board of Visitors (full group) Dinner, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_228; 128.8 MB 63 Digital Files
    - President: 3/22/06 @ 1:30 PM Standish Room Joe Persico Press Conference, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_229; 96.3 MB 49 Digital Files
    - President: 3/23/06 @ 8 AM - 5 PM location TBA Tracy Kidder / Albany Reading Project, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_230; 77.1 MB 39 Digital Files
    - President: 3/9/06 @ 3 PM - 4 PM Standish Room Linda Greenhouse class, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_231; 21.5 MB 10 Digital Files
    - President: 3/23/06 @ 5:30 PM - 8:30 PM Albany Court of Appeals President Hall lecturing / Judge Judith Kaye, 2006 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_232; 306.9 MB 105 Digital Files
    - University Development: 3/3/06 @ 9:30 AM PAC visiting Albany HS students on tour of campus, 2006 March 17; nam_ua395-6.1_233; 75.7 MB 37 Digital Files
    - Jewish Studies: 5/3/06 afternoon and evening Hastings-on-Hudson Jewish Studies Celebration Dinner, 2006 March 22; nam_ua395-6.1_234; 483.4 MB 203 Digital Files
    - Library: 5/2/06 @ 2 PM - 4 PM Standish Room Bread and Roses Celebration, 2006 April 3; nam_ua395-6.1_235; 187.4 MB 89 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 3/22/06 @ 6:30 PM Pres Res Joe Persico Reception, 2006 April 5; nam_ua395-6.1_236; 153.6 MB 70 Digital Files
    - President: 3/22/06 @ 11:45 PM Science Library President for a Day_Vincent Porfirio:, 2006 April 5; nam_ua395-6.1_237; 14.8 MB 7 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 3/22/06 @ Noon Science Library / Special Archives Conference Room Joe Persico Luncheon, 2006 April 5; nam_ua395-6.1_238; 53.3 MB 27 Digital Files
    - President: 3/21/06 @ 6:15 PM Albany H S press conference:, 2006 April 5; nam_ua395-6.1_239; 125.7 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Library: 3/24/06 @ 10:30 AM CC Ballroom Africa and the Diaspora: Agents for Change, 2006 April 6; nam_ua395-6.1_240; 93.9 MB 44 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 3/29/06 @ 9:30 AM East Campus / Cancer Ctr - Executive Board Rm 3rd Fl check presentation: First Niagara Bank Foundation, 2006 April 6; nam_ua395-6.1_241; 81.6 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 5/1/06 @ 5 PM RACC Great Dane Awards, 2006 April 12; nam_ua395-6.1_242; 637.0 MB 137 Digital Files
    - Research: 5/30/06 @ 12:15 Life Science Conferece Rm 1143 / 3 PM Life Science / Auditorium Research Colloquium, 2006 April 12; nam_ua395-6.1_243; 338.4 MB 77 Digital Files
    - Arts and Sciences: 4/21/06 @ 3:30 PM SS 369 group photo: students, faculty members and Chair, 2006 May 4; nam_ua395-6.1_244; 27.0 MB 10 Digital Files
    - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; nam_ua395-6.1_245; 1.2 GB 597 Digital Files
    - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; nam_ua395-6.1_246; 1.2 GB 597 Digital Files
    - President: 4/26/06 @ 8:30 AM President's Office President for a Day: Elizabeth Gray, 2006 May 10; nam_ua395-6.1_247; 64.3 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; nam_ua395-6.1_248; 1.2 GB 597 Digital Files
    - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; nam_ua395-6.1_249; 1.2 GB 597 Digital Files
    - Information Technology Services: 5/23/06 @ 9 - 10:30 AM Management Services Bldg staff meeting and group shot, 2006 May 18; nam_ua395-6.1_250; 255.8 MB 59 Digital Files
    - Information Technology Services: 5/23/06 @ 9 - 10:30 AM Management Services Bldg staff meeting and group shot, 2006 May 18; nam_ua395-6.1_251; 255.8 MB 59 Digital Files
    - President: 5/10/06 @ 6 PM Pres Res Valedictorian Dinner, 2006 May 24; nam_ua395-6.1_252; 143.3 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Development Events: 6/3/06 @ 3:45 PM Pres Res President's Club Reception, 2006 June 13; nam_ua395-6.1_253; 205.3 MB 96 Digital Files
    - Student Success: 6/12/06 @ Noon - 2 PM Science Library / West Seminar Room Albany High School Student Award Luncheon, 2006 June 14; nam_ua395-6.1_254; 112.9 MB 60 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 6/8/06 @ 4 PM location TBA University Council Meeting, 2006 June 15; nam_ua395-6.1_255; 137.3 MB 69 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 6/15/06 @ 8 PM Location TBA Special Olympics / Opening Ceremony, 2006 June 16; nam_ua395-6.1_256; 616.9 MB 197 Digital Files
    - President: 6/6/06 - 6/7/06 Long Island, NY various locations Roads Scholar Tour / Long Island, 2006 June 22; nam_ua395-6.1_257; 2.5 GB 471 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 6/13/06 @ 5:30 PM Nano Fab steps group: Jiangsu (China) visitors, 2006 June 26; nam_ua395-6.1_258; 39.8 MB 26 Digital Files
    - President: 6/14/06 @ 11:30 AM Standish Room Laval Delegation, 2006 June 27; nam_ua395-6.1_259; 57.9 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Advancement Events`: 6/2/06 @ 8 AM Ft. Orange Club / Albany, NY CEO Breakfast, 2006 July 3; nam_ua395-6.1_260; 131.8 MB 52 Digital Files
    - Advancement: s: 7/7/06 Campus Center / Parent's Fountain portraits: Tom Bessette and Cathy Hornberger Fall 2006 UAlbany Magazine, 2006 July 20; nam_ua395-6.1_261; 193.3 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Development Events: 8/14/06 @ 5 PM - 7:30 PM Standish Room / Giant's Practice NY Giant's Donor Reception, 2006 July 24; nam_ua395-6.1_262; 43.6 MB 47 Digital Files
    - ETAP: 7/25/06 @ 11 AM SUNY Tunes kids doing a recording, 2006 August 8; nam_ua395-6.1_263; 341.5 MB 164 Digital Files
    - Sports Information: 7/26/06 @ 11:30 AM Giant's Dutch Quad Lawn Giant's Media Day, 2006 August 9; nam_ua395-6.1_264; 157.1 MB 124 Digital Files
    - Development Events: 9/21/06 @ 5:30 PM Hall of Springs, Saratoga, NY 2006 Citizen Laureate, 2006 August 10; nam_ua395-6.1_265; 438.8 MB 229 Digital Files
    - Development Events: 9/21/06 @ 5:30 PM Hall of Springs, Saratoga, NY 2006 Citizen Laureate, 2006 August 10; nam_ua395-6.1_266; 438.8 MB 229 Digital Files
    - Business: 9/5/06 @ 12 Noon Parent's Fountain Connections Cover Shot, 2006 August 14; nam_ua395-6.1_267; 160.5 MB 61 Digital Files
    - Advancement: 9/18/06 @ 10 AM RACC Kermit Hall Tribute, 2006 October 2; nam_ua395-6.1_268; 519.1 MB 229 Digital Files
    - President: Photo Session: 8/14/06 CC Small Fountain President Kermit Hall Memorial, 2006 October 2; nam_ua395-6.1_269; 244.5 MB 173 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 10/3/06 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom for Fall Faculty meeting., 2006 October 3; nam_ua395-6.1_270; 151.2 MB 82 Digital Files
    - Development: 10/6/06 @ 2:30 pm University Hall 208C (Check presentation of Mr. Jack Davis from Dell to Chris Haile and Deb Read), 2006 October 6; nam_ua395-6.1_271; 36.5 MB 19 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 10/16/06 @ 10:30 AM University Hall Atrium; 10:45 AM Brief Program; 11 AM of People touring the building and any outside shot if needed all for University Hall Open House., 2006 October 16; nam_ua395-6.1_272; 110.7 MB 57 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 10/18/06 @ 8:30 am at Albany High School for Albany High School Teach Out, 2006 October 18; nam_ua395-6.1_273; 26.5 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Center for Autism: 10/18/06 @ 11 AM Desmond Hotel for Autism conference., 2006 October 18; nam_ua395-6.1_274; 36.0 MB 18 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 10/20/06 @ 12-1:30 pm CC Ballroom for Alumni Awareness Kick off event, 2006 October 19; nam_ua395-6.1_275; 201.9 MB 94 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 10/20/06 @ 12-1:30 pm CC Ballroom for Alumni Awareness Kick off event, 2006 October 19; nam_ua395-6.1_276; 201.9 MB 94 Digital Files
    - Development: 10/20/06 @ 2-3:30 Page Hall for Mental Health Forum for SSW 40th Anniversary., 2006 October 20; nam_ua395-6.1_277; 71.3 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Development: 10/20/06 @ 4:45 - 5:45 Milne 200 for SSW 40th Anniversary event, 2006 October 20; nam_ua395-6.1_278; 149.5 MB 73 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 10/5/06 @ 2 PM UAB Emeritus Center / Ray Ortali, Bill Reese and Toby Clyman, 2006 October 20; nam_ua395-6.1_279; 52.7 MB 30 Digital Files
    - Development: 10/21/06 @ 9:30 - 11 am Standish Room for Alumni Weekend event - Presidents Club Champagne Brunch, 2006 October 21; nam_ua395-6.1_280; 23.7 MB 72 Digital Files
    - Development: 10/25/06 @ 4-8:30 pm NYC for Foundation Board meeting and reception., 2006 October 25; nam_ua395-6.1_281; 212.8 MB 119 Digital Files
    - Development: 10/25/06 @ 4-8:30 pm NYC for Foundation Board meeting and reception., 2006 October 25; nam_ua395-6.1_282; 21.4 MB 61 Digital Files
    - Governmental Public and Media Relations: 10/18/06 @ 10 AM University Hall Atrium for McNulty Press Event / NERFI Dept of Justice Grant, 2006 October 26; nam_ua395-6.1_283; 134.8 MB 69 Digital Files
    - NYLARNET: 11/3/06 @ 9:45 - 10:30 AM Campus Center Assembly Hall for Latino Immigration Policy Conference, 2006 November 3; nam_ua395-6.1_284; 102.8 MB 53 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 11/1/06 @ 4 PM Emeritus Center (UAB?) for Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2006 November 4; nam_ua395-6.1_285; 66.7 MB 38 Digital Files
    - Development: 11/9/06 from 5:30 - 7:30, Art Museum for Donor Recognition Reception., 2006 November 9; nam_ua395-6.1_286; 165.5 MB 83 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 11/14/06 @ 1 - 2 PM Patroon Room for photo of Professor Angie Chung and Food for Thought program, 2006 November 14; nam_ua395-6.1_287; 32.5 MB 15 Digital Files
    - Development: 11/15/06 from 5:30 - 7:30 pm, Liife Sciences building for Life Sciences Donor Recognition event., 2006 November 15; nam_ua395-6.1_288; 24.1 MB 58 Digital Files
    - President's Office: photo shoot: 11/13/06 @ 4:30 PM in Sub-Basement Studio for Holiday Card, 2006 November 15; nam_ua395-6.1_289; 150.6 MB 179 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 11/29/06 @ 3 p.m. Art Museum for photo of a dress rehearsal of a performance marking the 35th anniversary of the Women's Studies department at UAlbany, 2006 November 30; nam_ua395-6.1_290; 36.9 MB 25 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 12/11/06 @ 10:30 am UNH Atrium for photo of Whitney Sperrazza addressing the prospective student tour., 2006 December 12; nam_ua395-6.1_291; 77.7 MB 39 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 12/12/06 @ 8 pm Recording Studios of the Lecture Center Sub-basement for photo of Whitney Sperrazza rehearsing with Serendipity., 2006 December 13; nam_ua395-6.1_292; 77.2 MB 42 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 12/13/06 @ 12 Noon Standish Room for photo of Valedictorian Luncheon 12/13/06 @ 2:30 p.m. UNH Atrium for Faculty/staff holiday party, 2006 December 14; nam_ua395-6.1_293; 25.4 MB 62 Digital Files
    - Small Business Development: 01/03/07 @ 10 a.m. Goold Orchards 1297 Brookview Station Road, Castleton, NY for photo of company., 2007 January 4; nam_ua395-6.1_294; 232.4 MB 105 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 01/11/07 at 2 p.m. UAB 437 for PDP Open House., 2007 January 11; nam_ua395-6.1_295; 80.7 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Center for Autism: 2/1 /07 @ 4:00 pm 1535 Western Ave for Center for Autism ribbon cutting. Types of shots needed: pictures of the ribbon cutting, during the reception, of the building out from with our sign, and a picture of the staff with the Dean and Provost. Need photos in both and hi and low res, 2007 February 2; nam_ua395-6.1_296; 38.4 MB 106 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 2/2/07 @ 12 - 1:30 PM SEFCU Arena for photo Lee McElroy Contract Signing, 2007 February 2; nam_ua395-6.1_297; 39.5 MB 90 Digital Files
    - Chancellor's Office: 3/1/07 @ 11 AM - 1:30 PM Fireside Lounge, Campus Center for Chancellor's Listening Tour, 2007 March 1; nam_ua395-6.1_298; 30.6 MB 81 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 4/27/07 @ 10:30 AM UNH Atrium for Design Entry Media Event, 2007 March 6; nam_ua395-6.1_299; 45.2 MB 47 Digital Files
    - Provost's Office: 3/7/07 @ 4 PM University Hall Atrium for photos of Susan Herbst shaking hands with students or a group shot of Susan with some students., 2007 March 7; nam_ua395-6.1_300; 26.1 MB 60 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 3/15/07 @ 4 - 5 P.M. at the Downtown Campus in Milne 215 for photo of the Campus Book Project Reading Discussion Group, 2007 March 14; nam_ua395-6.1_301; 15.7 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 3/16/07 @ 12:15 PM Campus Center (exact location tbd) for photos of students watching the UAlbany Basketball v Vermont., 2007 March 16; nam_ua395-6.1_302; 62.8 MB 127 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 3/28/07 @ 9 AM corner of Washington & Quail for Safe Corridor Press Event (series of speakers), 2007 March 29; nam_ua395-6.1_303; 110.2 MB 99 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 4/20/07 @ 11 a.m. University Hall Atrium for Biodiversity Event announcement., 2007 April 20; nam_ua395-6.1_304; 28.2 MB 39 Digital Files
    - PSC: Photo session - picture of new Psych. Services Center Building for inclusion in 2 brochures (job #'s 20004982 and 4983), 2007 April 23; nam_ua395-6.1_305; 82.2 MB 124 Digital Files
    - President's Office: 4/17/07 @ 5 PM Small Fountain for Candle Light Vigil., 2007 April 23; nam_ua395-6.1_306; 18.2 MB 54 Digital Files
    - Provost: 4/23/07 @ 3 - 5 PM Campus Center Ballroom for Award of Excellence ceremony, 2007 April 23; nam_ua395-6.1_307; 21.5 MB 43 Digital Files
    - Alumni Association: Photo Session; various locations for Alumni Weekend_07; email to follow with specific locations and times, 2007 April 24; nam_ua395-6.1_308; 375.2 MB 469 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 4/30/07 @ 2:30 PM meet at Standish Room and then photograph as they tour School of Education and Uptown Campus for News in Photos., 2007 April 26; nam_ua395-6.1_309; 26.4 MB 54 Digital Files
    - Center for Women in Government: 4/25/07, Campus Center Ballroom for Language Access Conference during the following times: 9 - 10:30 a.m. for Welcome and Keynote 12:30 - 1:30 p.m. for lunch presentation 4:15 - 5:15 p.m for final session, concluding remarks, and full group photo, 2007 April 26; nam_ua395-6.1_310; 219.7 MB 150 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/17/07 @ 11:30 AM 299 Washington Ave Albany, NY Psychological Services Center Re-Opening Celebration, 2007 April 30; nam_ua395-6.1_311; 37.1 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/16/07 @ 3 PN CC Small Fountain Holocaust Rememberance w/ Susan Herbst reading names of survivors, 2007 April 30; nam_ua395-6.1_312; 36.2 MB 33 Digital Files
    - Media and Marketing: 4/17/07 @ 11:30 AM 299 Washington Ave Albany, NY Psychological Services Center Re-Opening Celebration, 2007 April 30; nam_ua395-6.1_313; 37.1 MB 40 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 5/9/07 @ 5 PM (will confirm) University Hall Atrium for Stone Exhibit event., 2007 May 2; nam_ua395-6.1_314; 43.6 MB 72 Digital Files
    - Libraries: 5/3/07 @ 2 - 4 pm Standish Room, Science Library for Bread and Roses event, 2007 May 3; nam_ua395-6.1_315; 189.2 MB 101 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 5/14/07 @ 11:45 AM - 1 PM, Marriott Hotel for Citizen Bank check presentation to University., 2007 May 14; nam_ua395-6.1_316; 15.8 MB 31 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 6/18 @ 9:15 AM Campus Center, 2nd Floor for Alcohol Summit News Conference with Mayor, Chancellor and Officer in Charge Susan Herbst., 2007 June 18; nam_ua395-6.1_317; 86.8 MB 122 Digital Files
    - NEPHLI: 7/17/07 @ 12 Noon Rensselaerville Institute, 2007 July 17; nam_ua395-6.1_318; 54.1 MB 138 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing:; Alumni Awareness luncheon, campus ctr ballroom on Oct. 12th noon - 2 p.m., 2007 August 14; nam_ua395-6.1_319; 376.4 MB 186 Digital Files
    - Informatics: MSIS faculty and master students 8/28/07 from 12 - 1:30 p.m. in MILNE 200, just general shots of interaction, 2007 August 31; nam_ua395-6.1_320; 24.1 MB 63 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: photos in front of small fountain for Kermit Hall's remeberence ceremony, 2007 September 7; nam_ua395-6.1_321; 98.5 MB 79 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: photos of Chinese ambassador with his group as well as with Susan Herbst on 9/5/07. Event starts at 3 p.m. in UHALL atrium, please arrive earlier since you have a shoot at athletics at 3:45 p.m., 2007 September 13; nam_ua395-6.1_322; 23.8 MB 48 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: Mara-Tisch field naming on 8/17/07 @ 4 p.m., 2007 September 19; nam_ua395-6.1_323; 112.0 MB 138 Digital Files
    - Advancement Events: 10/13/07 from 9:30 - 11:00 a.m. in the Standish Room, Champagne Jazz Brunch., 2007 September 26; nam_ua395-6.1_324; 56.4 MB 103 Digital Files
    - Advancement Events: 11/8/07 from 6 - 9 p.m.@ the Hall of Springs in Saratoga for the Citizen Laureate Awards., 2007 September 26; nam_ua395-6.1_325; 108.3 MB 201 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 9/17/07 @ 1 p.m. in the Assembly Hall to take shot of Steve Kroft talking w/students, then on to the Medallion ceremony in the Fireside lounge @ 2:30 to get shots of him receiving medallion., 2007 September 28; nam_ua395-6.1_326; 97.8 MB 131 Digital Files
    - 9/20/07 @ 9 a.m. Apt. 215 Heritage Rd. Apts., go to intersection of route 20 and route 155, turn south on to route 155 and take left to heritage village, go to end of heritage rd. 3 story apt. bldg, apt. 215. call 452-5429 if you need assistance. * Please bring a back drop! * Is looking for a shot of the 11 books he wrote all in one photo., 2007 October 1; nam_ua395-6.1_327; 35.0 MB 13 Digital Files
    - University Events: 12/8/07 from 6 - 9 p.m. at the SEFCU Arena, Gala honoring Mayor Jennings, 2007 October 25; nam_ua395-6.1_328; 479.3 MB 483 Digital Files
    - Media & Marketing: 10/19/07 at 1 p.m. to take photos fof purple path ground breaking ceremony. Location is SEFCU Arena parking lot near Western Ave side., 2007 October 25; nam_ua395-6.1_329; 36.8 MB 61 Digital Files